Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyenpham-quoc (LinkedIn) github.com/PhamNguyen97 (Personal)

Top Skills

Project Management Time Series Analysis Natural Language Processing (NLP)

Languages

English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Foundations of Project Management

NGUYEN PHAM QUOC

Al Lead at TMT Ho Chi Minh City Vietnam

Summary

With background of automation engineering, I have developed my carrier as an AI

Engineer and then an Al Researcher. I have experience solving industrial problems

in both Computer Vision and Natural Language Processing. In addition to research

techniques, I can also perform task management and planning skills as a research

team leader.

Experience

TMT

Al Lead

December 2021 - Present (3 years 4 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Viettel High Tech

2 years 2 months

Al Research Lead

June 2021 - April 2022 (11 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Leader of Research team. Working on NLP, Time series and Computer vision tasks.

Machine Learning Engineer
March 2020 - April 2022 (2 years 2 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

VietAl

Teaching Assistant

July 2019 - December 2020 (1 year 6 months)

Ho Chi Minh

Gtopia

Machine Learning Engineer May 2019 - January 2020 (9 months)

District 10, Ho Chi Minh City

Ben Thanh Automation CO. Ltd Internship Trainee June 2018 - August 2018 (3 months) Tan Binh District, Ho Chi Minh City

Education

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology Master's degree, Computer Science · (2020)

Ho Chi Minh University of Technology
Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Automation Engineer · (2015 - 2019)

school.coders.tokyo Online Course Web development · (2019 - 2019)

VietAl

Machine Learning · (2019 - 2019)